Wyler, Julius; Papers ger102
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Course and research notes and materials, Undated; 6; 91 file folders
  - National Income -- Indexes, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 2)
  - National Income and War Finances, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 3)
  - Reading notes, general, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 4)
  - Reading notes -- Rostock, Hiltpold, Wunderlich, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 5)
  - The Structure of the World Economy, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 6)
  - The Structure of the World Economy. Deleted pages, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 7)
  - The Structure of the World Economy. Bibliography, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 8)
  - Statistical reports - Switzerland, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 9)
  - Swiss Democracy, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 10)
  - Swiss Democracy, Habsburg. Clippings, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 11)
  - United Nations. Statistics of National Income and Expenditure, 1951 (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 12)
  - USSR -- Consumption, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 13)
  - USSR -- Early notes, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 14)
  - USSR -- National Income, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 15)
  - USSR -- Statistics, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 16)
  - USSR. Clippings, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous publications, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 18)